learnforexlive.com 2012-10-05

# Learn Forex Live - Privacy Policy

Privacy Notice Table Of Contents: 

* Our Commitment To Privacy 
* The Information We Collect 
* How We Use Information 
* Our Commitment To Data Security 
* Our Commitment To Children's Privacy 
* How To Access Or Correct Your Information 
* How To Contact Us 

Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

The Information We Collect: 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

\- Name   
\- Email address 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you want to sent information regarding our services directly to another recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's name and email address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information used (but not kept) are: 

\- Name   
\- Email Address 

| 

The Way We Use Information: 

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing a request/order only to complete that request/order. We do not share this information with outside parties unless required to do so by law. 

We use the information you provide about someone else to inform them of our services. We do not share this information with outside parties unless required to do so by law. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive information as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

Our Commitment To Data Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Our Commitment To Children's Privacy: 

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us [here ](http://www.forexinfinitypro.com/contact.php) We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
